Lizzie: It is truth universally acknowledged that a single man
in possession of a good fortune
must be in want of a wife.
My mom gave each of us one of these last Christmas.
I have yet to wear it...
…ever.
Who am I? I'm a 24 year old grad student with
a mountain of student loans,
living at home and preparing for a career.
But to my mom, the only thing that matters is that I'm single.
My name is Lizzie Bennet and this is my life.
"My Name is Lizzie Bennet"
Written by Bernie Su
So my Mom belongs to a class of parents
I like to call the 2.5 WPF Club.
What's the 2.5 WPF Club? It stands for a home with 2.5 kids
and a white picket fence.
Which I know actually sounds pretty nice.
But it's really annoying when it's all your mom talks about 24/7.
Not only is my mom a member of the 2.5 WPF club,
she's probably the president.
How do I know? Ladies and the gentlemen, I present again…
Exhibit A.
Universal Truth, really?
I'm sure there are a great number of rich, young,
single men who aren't looking for wives.
In fact, let's examine the percentages.
Sleezeballs and scumbags,
Incapable of escaping current dead-end relationships,
sailing around the world trying to find themselves,
focusing on work, or skills, or hobbies, or whatever it is
that rich guys do when they're young.
But no. According to mother, every rich, single guy is
put on this planet to impregnate her daughters.
To illustrate my point, I'll need a little help.
Charlotte: What are you doing?
Lizzie: This is my friend Charlotte, and
she's going to help me with this demo.
Charlotte: No I'm not. What is this from?
Lizzie: Here, okay, your lines.
Charlotte: Who wrote this?
Lizzie: Shakespeare.
Honey! did you hear the house in
Netherfield sold the other day?
Charlotte: Did it now?
Lizzie: The large mansion with the white picket fence and
plenty of space to raise 2.5 grandkids.
Charlotte: Mmmhmm
Lizzie: Emily Lu told me. She said the deal was for three million
dollars! But it's not the price that matters, but who bought it.
Charlotte: As you say, my dear.
Lizzie: He's a well-mannered young man
from Harvard, working to become a doctor.
I hear his family has quite the fortune. How perfect for our girls!
Charlotte: How so?
Lizzie: Oh my dear husband! Can't you
imagine him with one of our daughters?
Charlotte: I find that rather difficult,
since I have yet to meet this young man.
Lizzie: Then you must go meet him at once!
Welcome him to the neighborhood.
I will bake a pie. Let him know about our three eligible
young daughters who are in desperate need of a rich, single man.
Look, I'm all for rich, single guys, but who
is my mom to tell one of us who to marry?
What if he's gay? What if he's a serial killer?
What if he's a gay serial killer?
I've got other things to worry about.
It's not like we're all going to put our lives on hold because some rich single guy dropped from the sky.
Lydia: Lizzie! Did mom tell you about who just
bought that mansion in Netherfield?
Lizzie: Haven't heard a word about it.
Lydia: So this... wait. What are you guys doing?
Lizzie: Making a video.
Everyone this is my sister, Lydia.
Lydia: Anyway, so this guy, his name is Bing Lee,
and he is rich, hot, annndd...
Lizzie: Let me guess... single?
Lydia: Jackpot, right?!? Whaaaat!
Lizzie: No.
Lydia: Whaaaaat. Yesss.